{
    "id": "e2404603384e47d3a3070ef34cec9480",
    "title": "Kinds Of Nouns",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Always speak the truth. Truth is a/an ..................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "common noun",
                "proper noun",
                "abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "5a7726d4ee6f4453a42dca270874c80d"
        },
        {
            "question": "Honesty is the best policy. Honesty is a/an ...................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "collective noun",
                "common noun",
                "abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "17b81c0e0dad4f86ab90d7af2d5a047a"
        },
        {
            "question": "King Solomon was famous for his wisdom. Solomon is a/an ..........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "proper noun",
                "common noun",
                "abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2e0ee2adeb4845e8ad8b6e6b2212f1cf"
        },
        {
            "question": "A committee of five was appointed. Committee is a/an ......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "common noun",
                "collective noun",
                "proper noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "7906565083574db994b18392c7c8b1d9"
        },
        {
            "question": "We saw a fleet of ships in the harbour. Fleet is a/an ...........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "common noun",
                "collective noun",
                "proper noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "449fb0c161b9497680b80f045e41f37d"
        },
        {
            "question": "He gave me a bunch of grapes. Bunch is a/an .....................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "common noun",
                "collective noun",
                "abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "eb310ac68b1f4cfabc160d368bad6fa8"
        },
        {
            "question": "London is on the river Thames. Thames is a/an ........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "proper noun",
                "common noun",
                "abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "854950e379784b7bb3a5e09a8b114f57"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cleanliness is next to godliness. Cleanliness is a/an ......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "common noun",
                "proper noun",
                "abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "4137064041af40c586e89220f01b3e7c"
        },
        {
            "question": "Wisdom is better than riches. Wisdom is a/an ...........................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "collective noun",
                "common noun",
                "abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "e2aefae34de5409b877220ba58efaab9"
        },
        {
            "question": "Winston Churchill was one of the greatest Prime Ministers of England. Prime ministers is a/an .......................................",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "common noun",
                "proper noun",
                "abstract noun"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "40e2b95fa315464888e6c4d160a6c71a"
        }
    ]
}